smashbeats.com 2013-12-09

# veopod - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting veopod.com. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for veopod.com only. If you visit other web sites through any links, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites. 

**Collection of Information** We collect personal information upon registration like name, email address, etc. This information is kept private unless specified otherwise. 

**Cookie/Tracking Technology** We use cookies and tracking technology for stats and also to store login information on your computer. Tracking technology is used to understand how visitors use this veopod.com and may be shared with third parties. 

**Distribution of Information** We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to companies for marketing purposes. 

**Commitment to Data Security** Your personal identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. 

**Privacy Contact Information** If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us. 

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted. 

**Notice Regarding Online Behavioral Advertising** We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice visit the NAI at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.
